<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adventures Unknown</title>
    <link>https://josh.buhler.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adventures Unknown</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 20:18:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://josh.buhler.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Climbing Miller Hill</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/afcanyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 20:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/afcanyon/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite things about living in Utah is how easy it can be to get out of the city, and get outdoorsy. Last week was one of those days where Drew and I got to take advantage of that proximity to nature. With the kids back in school, Cindy took advantage of her new found freedom to head up American Fork Canyon to do some paddleboarding on Tibble Fork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHIRP.</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/chirp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 20:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/chirp/</guid>
      <description>The more I use ham radio, the more I start to fine-tune and tweak my setup. Especially when it comes to the presets on the radio in my truck. I’ve spent a lot of time collecting the info and programming it into my radio, and I’d hate to lose that.
Mostly because I&#39;m a giant nerd, I eventually created a Git repository to store the backups of my preset info, and have hosted it on Github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control4 the Garage Door</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/c4-garage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 20:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/c4-garage/</guid>
      <description>When we first moved into our house, the home builder installed a set of Chamberlain myQ enabled smart garage door openers. I was excited about the possibility of being able to use my phone to make sure that our doors were closed when we were away, or to be notified if they opened when they shouldn&#39;t. The only piece missing was that our builder did not include the network modules needed to enable the smart functionality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand Staircase-Escalante National Monument</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/escalante-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/escalante-2019/</guid>
      <description>With spring on the way, the family was looking forward to our first big trip of the year, especially with our new camp trailer. While we really liked our popup trailer, we had just outgrown it a lot faster than we thought we would, and could use just a little more space. So earlier this year we traded in the popup for something a little bit bigger.
For the trailer’s maiden voyage, we decided to head down to Grand Staircase-Escalante National Monument.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tactical Tire Kit</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/tirebox/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 20:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/tirebox/</guid>
      <description>If you go off-road often, it&#39;s not a matter of if, but when you&#39;re going to need an air compressor, or some other source of compressed air. Whether it&#39;s for airing your tires back up before returning to pavement, or refilling a repaired tire, having a compressor with you is vital. Even if you don&#39;t plan on going off-road, it&#39;s still pretty handy being able to air up a tire now and then if you&#39;re out and about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science and Spirituality</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/science-spirituality/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 19:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/science-spirituality/</guid>
      <description>Science is not only compatible with spirituality; it is a profound source of spirituality. When we recognize our place in an immensity of light-years and in the passage of ages, when we grasp the intricacy, beauty, and subtlety of life, then that soaring feeling, that sense of elation and humility combined, is surely spiritual. So are our emotions in the the presence of great art or music or literature, or of acts of exemplary selfless courage such as those of Mohandas Gandhi or Martin Luther King, Jr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What matters.</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/what-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 13:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/what-matters/</guid>
      <description>Find out what makes you kinder, what opens you up and brings out the most loving, generous, and unafraid version of you — and go after those things as if nothing else matters.
Because, actually, nothing else does.
— George Saunders</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Big Boy Scout Camp</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/welcome-to-big-boy-scout-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 14:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/welcome-to-big-boy-scout-camp/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month, I was able to attend the first annual Expedition Utah Overland Skills Camp, which my wife and I began to affectionately refer to as “big boy scout camp”. No merit badges, but lots of time spent out camping with a bunch of guys off learning new skills.
The event began for me by waking up Friday morning at 6:00AM so that I could arrive in Price, UT by 9:00AM for a trail ride to the event site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kachow!</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/kachow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 01:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/kachow/</guid>
      <description>The Pinewood Derby was always one of my favorite things about being a cub scout. Even when I moved on to boy scouts, it was always a bit of a bummer that we didn&#39;t get to participate anymore.
Fast forward a few years, and I&#39;m now the Webelos den leader of our pack. And that means… Pinewood Derby! While Drew isn&#39;t quite old enough to officially join the pack yet, for all intents and purposes, we consider him an honorary member of our den, as he attends every meeting faithfully with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another 100 Miles of Heaven and Hell</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/another-100-miles-of-heaven-and-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 00:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/another-100-miles-of-heaven-and-hell/</guid>
      <description>Clearly I&#39;m terrible at posting on a regular basis, as it&#39;s been over a year since my last post. But once again, I recently had the opportunity to help with communications for the Wasatch Front 100 Mile Endurance Run.
This year was very similar to last year, but we still had a lot of fun. I also got a chance to flex my ham nerd muscles a bit more, as this year I provided the packet system we&#39;d be using for the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 Miles of Heaven and Hell…</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/100-miles-of-heaven-and-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 14:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/100-miles-of-heaven-and-hell/</guid>
      <description>This weekend I had the opportunity to help out with some communications for the Wasatch Front 100 Mile Endurance Run. Just like the name says, it’s a 100 mile race, and the course has folks running from East Mountain Wilderness Park near Kaysville, UT down to Soldier Hollow in Wasatch Mountain State Park. Some friends of mine have been volunteering for this event for a few years now, and have asked me if I was interested in the past, but I haven’t been able to help until this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cecret Lake</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/cecret-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 13:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/cecret-lake/</guid>
      <description>The quieter you become, the more you can hear.
– Ram Dass</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Not Disturb</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/do-not-disturb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 01:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/do-not-disturb/</guid>
      <description>     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Reef - Are we there yet?</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/capitol-reef-are-we-there-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 21:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/capitol-reef-are-we-there-yet/</guid>
      <description>So far our plan to head south to escape the cold of Salt Lake wasn&#39;t working so well. While it was a bit warmer during the day down in the Capitol Reef area, the nights were still a bit chilly. Still, it was better than the 2-3 inches of snow we had left behind back home.
    Due to the chilly nights and running the heater in the trailer, we blew through a full tank of propane in just two nights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiking Capitol Reef</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/hiking-capitol-reef/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 05:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/hiking-capitol-reef/</guid>
      <description>Heading to Capitol Reef for spring break wasn&#39;t part of the plan. Originally, we had planned on going down to Zion National Park. However, our failure to plan ahead meant that getting a campsite for the weekend was fairly unlikely. So we adjusted our plans. Instead, we&#39;d head down to Arches, and spend some time exploring Moab as well. Not really thinking that one through much either, we soon realized that Easter Jeep Safari was happening that same weekend, so we&#39;d again have to adjust our plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ho ho ho…</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/ho-ho-ho/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 05:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/ho-ho-ho/</guid>
      <description>     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Lost</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/getting-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/getting-lost/</guid>
      <description>I may not always know where I am, or exactly where I&#39;m headed, but I&#39;ve never really been lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey. I’m Josh.
I’m just an average guy doing my thing out here in Herriman, Utah. I’ve been married to a beautiful girl for a while now, and together we’ve got three pretty awesome kids. There’s also a cat that for the most part, hates the world, but likes us for some reason.
My day job is at Control4, working as an iOS developer. Basically, we make some pretty killer home automation gear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Artsy-Fartsy Railroad Tour of 2016</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/the-artsy-fartsy-railroad-tour-of-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 18:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/the-artsy-fartsy-railroad-tour-of-2016/</guid>
      <description>This last weekend, a couple of friends and I took a trip along the Utah portion of the Transcontinental Railroad route. We planned to do a bit of sightseeing, as well as check out a few different bits of artwork along the way. I had been looking forward to this trip, as I’ve wanted to run this route for a while, but just hadn’t made it out there yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blacks Fork, UT</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/blacks-fork-ut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 19:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/blacks-fork-ut/</guid>
      <description>Fall break this year has been a bit of a staycation for us. Sleeping in, working on projects around the house, and just hanging out. One day, we took the Bronco for a drive up to the Uintas, just cruising up the Mirror Lake Highway.
    After getting a late start, we made our way up Parley&#39;s Canyon, grabbed a quick lunch in Park City, then continued on to Kamas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Moab Training Day</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/little-moab-training-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 23:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/little-moab-training-day/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend RME4x4.com hosted a training day down in the Little Moab area. I’ve never been down there, and I’m almost always up for a quick trip to learn something new.
We met up at the Chevron in Saratoga Springs, and once the group was assembled, we made the trek down to Cedar Valley. The night was spent camped out next to Chimney Rock, and a group of Boy Scouts (that wasn&#39;t planned).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost Town Tour 2016</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/ghost-town-tour-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 19:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/ghost-town-tour-2016/</guid>
      <description>“Well, they’re either out here lost too, or they’re out to murder us. Both seem likely right now.”
Luckily, the folks following us around the trails west of Milford, UT weren’t out to murder us that night, and as a result, I’m still here to tell this story.
When the trip reports from the 2015 Ghost Town Tour were posted to ExpeditionUtah.com, I was fairly jealous about having missed the trip.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>