<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Camping on Adventures Unknown</title>
    <link>https://josh.buhler.me/tags/camping/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Camping on Adventures Unknown</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 01:02:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://josh.buhler.me/tags/camping/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Grand Staircase-Escalante National Monument</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/escalante-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/escalante-2019/</guid>
      <description>With spring on the way, the family was looking forward to our first big trip of the year, especially with our new camp trailer. While we really liked our popup trailer, we had just outgrown it a lot faster than we thought we would, and could use just a little more space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tactical Tire Kit</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/tirebox/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 20:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/tirebox/</guid>
      <description>If you go off-road often, it&amp;rsquo;s not a matter of if, but when you&amp;rsquo;re going to need an air compressor, or some other source of compressed air. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s for airing your tires back up before returning to pavement, or refilling a repaired tire, having a compressor with you is vital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Big Boy Scout Camp</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/welcome-to-big-boy-scout-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 14:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/welcome-to-big-boy-scout-camp/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month, I was able to attend the first annual Expedition Utah Overland Skills Camp, which my wife and I began to affectionately refer to as “big boy scout camp”. No merit badges, but lots of time spent out camping with a bunch of guys off learning new skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another 100 Miles of Heaven and Hell</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/another-100-miles-of-heaven-and-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 00:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/another-100-miles-of-heaven-and-hell/</guid>
      <description>Clearly I&amp;rsquo;m terrible at posting on a regular basis, as it&amp;rsquo;s been over a year since my last post. But once again, I recently had the opportunity to help with communications for the Wasatch Front 100 Mile Endurance Run.
This year was very similar to last year, but we still had a lot of fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 Miles of Heaven and Hell…</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/100-miles-of-heaven-and-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 14:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/100-miles-of-heaven-and-hell/</guid>
      <description>This weekend I had the opportunity to help out with some communications for the Wasatch Front 100 Mile Endurance Run. Just like the name says, it’s a 100 mile race, and the course has folks running from East Mountain Wilderness Park near Kaysville, UT down to Soldier Hollow in Wasatch Mountain State Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Reef - Are we there yet?</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/capitol-reef-are-we-there-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 21:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/capitol-reef-are-we-there-yet/</guid>
      <description>So far our plan to head south to escape the cold of Salt Lake wasn&amp;rsquo;t working so well. While it was a bit warmer during the day down in the Capitol Reef area, the nights were still a bit chilly. Still, it was better than the 2-3 inches of snow we had left behind back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiking Capitol Reef</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/hiking-capitol-reef/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 05:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/hiking-capitol-reef/</guid>
      <description>Heading to Capitol Reef for spring break wasn&amp;rsquo;t part of the plan. Originally, we had planned on going down to Zion National Park. However, our failure to plan ahead meant that getting a campsite for the weekend was fairly unlikely. So we adjusted our plans. Instead, we&amp;rsquo;d head down to Arches, and spend some time exploring Moab as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Artsy-Fartsy Railroad Tour of 2016</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/the-artsy-fartsy-railroad-tour-of-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 18:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/the-artsy-fartsy-railroad-tour-of-2016/</guid>
      <description>This last weekend, a couple of friends and I took a trip along the Utah portion of the Transcontinental Railroad route. We planned to do a bit of sightseeing, as well as check out a few different bits of artwork along the way. I had been looking forward to this trip, as I’ve wanted to run this route for a while, but just hadn’t made it out there yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Moab Training Day</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/little-moab-training-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 23:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/little-moab-training-day/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend RME4x4.com hosted a training day down in the Little Moab area. I’ve never been down there, and I’m almost always up for a quick trip to learn something new.
We met up at the Chevron in Saratoga Springs, and once the group was assembled, we made the trek down to Cedar Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost Town Tour 2016</title>
      <link>https://josh.buhler.me/post/ghost-town-tour-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 19:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://josh.buhler.me/post/ghost-town-tour-2016/</guid>
      <description>“Well, they’re either out here lost too, or they’re out to murder us. Both seem likely right now.”
Luckily, the folks following us around the trails west of Milford, UT weren’t out to murder us that night, and as a result, I’m still here to tell this story.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
